East Rutherford, NJ 07073

□+1 (551) 206-0263 | ■ anthonyfreay@gmail.com | ♠ www.anthonyfreay.com | □ anthonyfreay I anthonyfreay

Summary _

A software engineer who uses curiosity and drive to solve problems and improve technical skills. Actively pursuing a full-time software engineering / full-stack developer position. Recent internship experiences at BNY Mellon has given exposure to how an application is designed, developed, and deployed within a wide-scale enterprise environment, as well as the importance of Test-Driven Development. Always ready to learn new technologies and continually grow by pursuing technical and non-technical challenges.

Education

Villanova University (VU)

May 2020

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & PSYCHOLOGY

Villanova, PA

Awards: O'Toole Presidential Scholar

Completed Courses: Data Structures & Algorithms I & II, Platform-Based Computing, Computer Systems I & II, Discrete Structures, Analysis of Algorithms, Theory of Computation, Information Visualization, Database Systems,

& Software Engineering

Current Courses: Human-Computer Interaction

Skills

Advanced: Java, Golang, HTML/CSS/JS **Programming**

Intermediate: ReactJS, OpenAPI Spec (Swagger)

Deployments Intermediate: Docker, Artifactory **Databases** Intermediate: MongoDB, MySQL Languages English (native), Spanish (fluent)

Work Experience _____

BNY Mellon Jun. 2018 - Aug. 2018

Jersey City, NJ SUMMER TECHNOLOGY ANALYST

• Overview: Given freedom to fully design, develop, and deploy a full-stack URL shortening service using Golang, ReactJS, MongoDB, Nginx, and Docker company-wide, reaching 35 countries and 52,000 employees

- Front-end: Developed with a minimal design using ReactJS
- Back-end: RESTful API developed using Golang, visually documented using Swagger, and utilized MongoDB to store mapped URLs

BNY Mellon Jun. 2019 - Aug. 2019

SUMMER TECHNOLOGY ANALYST New York, NY

• Overview: Develop and deploy an automated regression test of an API user interface leveraging Java and Selenium Webdriver

Leadership _____

SENOIR STAFF MEMBER

Villanova University Tech Crew (VUTC)

Aug. 2017 - Present

· Assist in the facilitation of VU's event production needs and on-boarding new members

Villanova, PA

- In the 2018-19 academic year, produced 31 events including Orientation, Special Olympics, and Commencement
- Resident content creator for all social media platforms

Projects _

Redesigning and optimizing URL shortening service simple-url

personal-site Designed, developed, and deployed personal-site to improve web development skills and increase digital presence

Hobbies _